What will you have?
Ne alırsın?
The usual.
Her zamankinden.
Your usual? I forgot what that is.
Her zamanki mi? Unuttum.
When are you going to remember, Robbie?
Ne zaman hatırlayacaksın Robbie?
Hamburger, double cheese, extra ketchup, thick-sliced tomatoes.
Hamburger, çift peynirli, ekstra ketçap, kalın dilimli domates.
Slip in pickles, and you're dead.
Turşu koyarsan gebertirim.
You expect me to remember that?
Bunu aklımda tutmamı mı bekliyorsun?
That Chinese or Vietnamese dude, he's been nosing around about you.
O Çinli veya Vietnamlı adam senin hakkında sorular soruyor.
He comes here a lot lately.
Şu aralar buraya çok sık geliyor.
He even asked me who you were.
Senin kim olduğunu bile sordu.
He's no Chinese or Vietnamese dude.
O adam ne Çinli ne de Vietnamlı.
Really?
Gerçekten mi?
I'm pretty sure he's Japanese.
Japon olduğuna eminim.
He's a neurosurgeon, and a damn fine one too.
Beyin cerrahı, üstelik çok da iyi bir cerrah.
Isn't that right, Dr. Tenma?
Öyle değil mi Dr. Tenma?
Answer me!
Cevap ver!
Your ex-fiancée was the daughter of the director of your hospital.
Eski nişanlın çalıştığın hastanenin müdürünün kızıydı, değil mi?
What are you going to do to Eva?
Eva'ya ne yapacaksın?
"Eva"?
Eva mı?
It's "Ms. Heinemann" to you, pal! You ain't engaged to her anymore.
Bayan Heinemann diyeceksin dostum. O kadın artık nişanlın değil.
Not only are you not a doctor anymore but you're also a fugitive.
Ayrıca sen de artık doktor değilsin, kanun kaçağısın.
Go to prison, serve your time and start over.
Hapse gir, cezanı çek ve baştan başla.
If you're a model inmate, you could even get out early.
Örnek bir mahkûm olursan erken çıkabilirsin.
Let Eva go!
Eva'yı bırak!
Let her go?
Bırakmak mı?
I ain't holding her against her will.
Onu zorla tutuyor değilim ya.
She's going to parties every day.
Her gün partilere gidiyor.
Let me see Eva!
Eva'yı göster bana!
Let you see her?
Göstereyim mi?
Hey! Don't go trashing my place.
Hey, mekânımı dağıtma.
Quit hanging around here. Now get lost.
Bir daha buraya gelme. Şimdi kaybol.
Eva…
Eva…
Get lost.
Kaybol.
Did you see Kenzo?
Kenzo'yu mu gördün?
Yes, a couple of days ago.
Evet, birkaç gün önce.
I thought I should at least tell you.
Sana söylemem gerek diye düşündüm.
He wants to see you.
Seni görmek istiyor.
You didn't beat him up, did you?
Onu dövmedin, değil mi?
No. I wouldn't do that.
Hayır, böyle bir şey yapmam.
-We're leaving. -Huh?
-Gidiyoruz. -Ne?
You're done with today's party already?
Bugünkü partide işin bitti mi?
Not just for today. I'm done with parties.
Sadece bugünkü partide değil, tüm partilerde işim bitti.
Probably.
Muhtemelen.
Well done, Eva.
Tebrikler Eva.
How about having dinner with me?
Benimle yemek yemeye ne dersin?
Sure.
Olur tabii.
So, you dropped her off at some restaurant,
Onu bir restorana bırakıp
but you came here for dinner?
yemek yemeye buraya mı geldin?
Compared to the food at those parties and high-class restaurants,
O partilerdeki, üst sınıf restoranlardaki yemeklere göre
the hamburgers here are way better.
buranın hamburgerleri misliyle daha iyi.
I'm not sure if that's a compliment or an insult.
Yerdin mi, övdün mü anlamadım.
You're getting annoying.
Sinirime dokunmaya başladın.
Do you want to get hurt again?
Yine dayak mı istiyorsun?
I thought I told you to get--
Sana bir daha buraya…
You behind the counter, freeze!
Tezgâhın arkasındaki, kıpırdama! Kıpırdarsan vururum.
We've got a dangerous doctor here.
Doktorumuz çok tehlikeliymiş.
Who hired you?
Seni kim tuttu?
I know your boss is The Baby.
Patronunun Bebek olduğunu biliyorum
But the man who ordered you to protect Eva
ama Eva'yı korumanı isteyen adam örgütte daha da yüksek konumda.
Who gave you your orders?
Kimden emir aldın?
I don't know who he is.
Kim olduğunu bilmiyorum.
But I know what he looks like.
Ama tipini biliyorum.
He's a man with glasses.
Gözlüklü bir adam.
A man with glasses?
Gözlüklü bir adam mı?
What is he making Eva do?
Eva'ya ne yaptırıyor?
Like I told you, he's just having Eva go to parties.
Söylediğim gibi, Eva'yı partilere gönderiyor sadece.
She eats, drinks then leaves. That's all.
Bir şeyler yiyor, içiyor ve gidiyor. Hepsi bu.
That can't be all!
Hepsi bu olamaz!
She must be doing something special at those parties!
O partilerde özel bir şey yapıyor olmalı!
No.
Hayır.
-Come to think of it, today… -Today?
-Bir düşününce bugün… -Bugün?
Never mind, it was nothing.
Boş ver, hiçbir şey değildi.
She pointed at someone.
Birine işaret etti.
She pointed at someone?
İşaret mi etti?
A young man.
Genç bir adama.
A young man?
Genç bir adama mı?
She went like this…
Şöyle yaptı,
and pointed at a young blonde man with a pretty face.
güzel güzlü, sarışın bir adama işaret etti.
But that was all.
Ama hepsi bu kadardı.
Where's Eva now?
Eva şu an nerede?
She's having dinner with that guy with glasses who hired me.
Beni tutan gözlüklü adamla yemek yiyor.
Where? Tell me now! Where are they?
Nerede? Hemen söyle! Neredeler?
Eva's job is over now!
Eva'nın işi bitti!
When this job is over, I'm sure I'll be murdered.
Bu iş bitince öldürüleceğime adım gibi eminim.
I'm done with parties.
Partilerle işim bitti.
Where is Eva?
Eva nerede?
Stop!
Dur!
Where is she?
Nerede o?
I sent her to her hotel.
Oteline gönderdim.
Do you have a gun?
Silahın var mı?
No… I never carry a gun.
Hayır, asla silah taşımam.
Then use this one.
Bunu kullan o zaman.
Kill her.
Öldür onu.
That night, the party was just like all the other ones we went to.
O geceki parti hep gittiğimiz partilere benziyordu.
The smell of liquor.
Alkol kokusu.
The smell of perfume.
Parfüm kokusu.
Empty laughter.
Boş kahkahalar.
It was the same as always.
Her zamanki gibiydi.
Except for that single moment.
O tek hareket dışında.
Eva pointed at a certain young man.
Eva bir gence işaret etti.
Then the man with glasses showed up with another well-dressed young man.
Sonra gözlüklü adam başka bir şık giyimli gençle geldi.
Then the two young men shook hands.
İki genç adam el sıkıştı.
I didn't notice it at the time, but that was when Eva's job ended.
O an fark etmedim ama Eva'nın işi o an bitmişti.
I figured it would be you who would kill me.
Beni senin öldüreceğini düşünmüştüm.
Go right ahead.
Durma hadi.
I've already gotten pretty drunk.
Zaten kör kütük sarhoşum.
I've got no more regrets either.
Başka pişmanlığım da kalmadı.
That's right.
Doğru ya.
You can't shoot me at this hotel, can you?
Beni bu otelde vuramazsın, değil mi?
You told me how when you shot your girlfriend,
Sevgilini vurmaya gittiğinde
you found yourself standing in a sea of blood.
kendini kan gölü içinde bulduğunu söylemiştin.
Take me outside when you shoot me.
Beni vuracaksan dışarı çıkar.
If you don't, they'll make you pay to clean the room.
Çıkarmazsan oda temizlik ücretini senden alırlar.
There is still one thing that I regret.
Hâlâ pişman olduğum bir konu var.
Although, I guess it doesn't matter.
Gerçi sanırım artık bir önemi yok.
Why the hell did I do that today anyway?
Bugün onu niye yaptım ki?
You saw me, right? When I pointed.
Beni gördün, değil mi? İşaret ettim.
I bet what I did today was pretty damn terrible.
Bugün yaptığım şeyin çok kötü olduğuna eminim.
I brought together some horrible people with the devil.
Çok kötü insanları iblisin ta kendisiyle buluşturdum.
Like bringing together Mephistopheles and Faust.
Mephistopheles'le Faust'u bir araya getirmek gibi.
But who cares anyway?
Ama kimin umurunda?
After what I did today, I won't be going to any more parties.
Bugün yaptığım o şeyden sonra başka partiye gitmeyeceğim.
But I've still got all these invitations to parties that are coming up.
Yaklaşan partilerin davetiyeleri daha duruyor.
If you'd like
İstersen
when I'm dead, why don't you check up on what I did?
ben öldüğümde gidip ne yaptığıma baksana.
All right, you may as well put an end to this.
Tamam, bitir bari şu işi.
Run away.
Kaç.
Run away with me.
Benimle kaç.
I think you've got me all wrong.
Sanırım beni yanlış anladın!
Run away with you? You can't be serious!
Seninle kaçayım mı? Ciddi olamazsın.
When did we get so close?
Ne ara bu kadar yakınlaştık?
I can't…
Artık…
I can't kill people anymore.
Artık insan öldüremem.
You can't kill people? But could you kill a devil?
İnsan öldüremez misin? Peki bir iblisi öldürebilir misin?
I'm a devil.
Ben bir iblisim.
That suit and necktie that I bought for you,
Sana aldığım takım elbise ve kravat
they're the same ones Kenzo wore long ago.
Kenzo'nun uzun zaman önce giyip taktıklarıyla aynı.
Don't you get it? I dressed you up to look like Kenzo Tenma.
Anlamıyor musun? Seni Kenzo Tenma gibi giydirdim.
Kill me!
Öldür beni!
Hurry up and kill me!
Hadisene, öldür beni!
Do it now!
Öldür hadi!
Hurry up and kill me.
Hadisene, öldür beni.
Unless you kill me soon…
Beni hemen öldürmezsen
then you'll be killed.
sen ölürsün.
I could kill a devil, huh?
Bir iblisi öldürebilirim, öyle mi?
Mom, wake up!
Anne, uyan!
I'll be just fine.
Düzeleceğim.
I just need to sleep this off for a bit.
Biraz uyusam geçer.
You can't! You'll die if you fall asleep here!
Olmaz, burada uyuyakalırsan ölürsün!
I'll be fine. Just leave me here a bit.
Bir şey olmaz, beni biraz bırak.
You sure look gloomy.
Çok üzgün görünüyorsun.
I always look gloomy.
Hep üzgün görünürüm.
Did anyone come looking for me?
Beni aramaya gelen oldu mu?
No, not a soul.
Hayır, kimse gelmedi.
But that Japanese guy left this with me last night.
Ama o Japon adam dün gece bunu bana bıraktı.
"Hellblau Hotel Room 205."
"Hellblau Otel, Oda 205"
He said to contact him there if you need anything.
Bir şeye ihtiyacın olursa ona ulaşmanı söyledi.
Do you want your usual?
Her zamankinden mi istersin?
No thanks.
Hayır, sağ ol.
If I fill up on some disgusting hamburger, I'll lose the will to go.
İğrenç bir hamburgerle karnımı doyurursam gitme isteğim kaçar.
Go where?
Nereye gitme?
A party.
Partiye.
It's crazy, ain't it?
Akıl kârı değil, değil mi?
With just a single necktie, they'll let you in anywhere.
Tek bir kravatla giremeyeceğin bir yer yok.
Just one of these…
Sadece bir kravatla…
There he is.
İşte orada.
So, that guy's a devil, huh?
Demek bu adam bir iblis.
He shook hands with so many people that his hand must be rubbed raw.
O kadar fazla insanla el sıkışıyor ki elleri nasır tutacak.
Then he left the party venue.
Sonra parti salonunu terk ediyor.
The sixth floor, eh?
Altıncı kat demek.
But which room is he in?
Ama hangi odada kalıyor?
Please go inside.
Lütfen içeri gel.
Please take a seat here.
Lütfen şöyle geç.
Make yourself comfortable.
Rahatına bak.
You want to meet him too, don't you?
Sen de onunla görüşmek istiyorsun.
"Him"?
Onunla mı?
I'm waiting for him too. He'll be here soon.
Ben de onu bekliyorum. Birazdan gelecek.
Let's talk a little until he arrives. Let's see, what should we talk about?
O gelene kadar sohbet edelim. Ne konuşsak ki?
I know.
Buldum.
Let's talk about the end of the world.
Dünyanın sonunu konuşalım.
The young punk happily blabbered on.
Genç serseri mutlulukla zırvaladı.
He talked like a child speaking to his parents
Anne babasına o gün okulda yaptığı eğlenceli şeyleri
about the fun he had at school that day.
anlatan bir çocuk gibiydi.
He just kept talking to me like that.
O şekilde benimle konuşup durdu.
"The end of the world," my ass.
Dünyanın sonuymuş.
The crazy young punk's talk was a bunch of nonsense.
Bu deli, genç serseri saçmalayıp durdu.
That's what I thought at the time.
O an böyle düşündüm.
What did you think? Pretty interesting, isn't it?
Ne düşünüyorsun? Çok ilgi çekici, değil mi?
Did you enjoy it, Martin?
Sevdin mi Martin?
How come you know my name?
Adımı nereden biliyorsun?
Here's an idea. Let's talk about you next.
Bir fikrim var, şimdi senden bahsedelim.
You've been working for The Baby for three years now.
Üç yıldır Bebek için çalışıyorsun.
Have you been looking into me?
Beni araştırdın mı?
Before that, you were in prison.
Ondan önce hapisteydin.
Those must have been a hard eight years.
Zor bir sekiz yıl olmalı ama örnek bir mahkûmdun, değil mi?
You got out pretty quickly for having been a murderer.
Bir katile göre çok kısa sürede çıktın.
Did you enjoy living with your girlfriend?
Sevgilinle yaşamak güzel miydi?
You know, the girlfriend you shot and killed. Her name was Edda.
Vurarak öldürdüğün sevgilinle. Adı Edda'ydı.
You've got pretty poor taste, pal.
Çok kötü zevkin var dostum.
She was a total drug addict, wasn't she?
Uyuşturucu bağımlısıydı, değil mi?
You did everything you could to get her off drugs.
Uyuşturucuyu bırakması için elinden geleni yaptın.
That's not easy to do.
Bu kolay bir iş değildir.
I guess you did it out of love.
Sanırım sevdiğinden yaptın.
Do you want to get hurt?
Dayak mı istiyorsun?
She got back on her feet.
Kız düzeldi.
She'd make you dinner and wait for you to come home.
Sana yemek yapıp eve gelmeni beklerdi. Birlikte mutlu bir hayat sürüyordunuz.
Do you want me to punch your lights out?
Yumruk atıp bayıltayım mı seni?
But one night, when you got home, you saw something that blew your mind.
Ama bir gece, eve döndüğünde aklını başından alan bir şey gördün.
Her ex-boyfriend was at your place.
Eski sevgilisi senin evindeydi.
She'd done drugs again,
Tekrar uyuşturucu kullanmıştı.
and while in a daze, she said to you over and over again,
Sersemken sana tekrar tekrar şöyle dedi,
"I'm sorry."
"Özür dilerim"
But you shot and killed both her and the man.
Ama hem onu hem de adamı vurup öldürdün.
At least that's how it came out in court.
En azından mahkemede böyle dedin.
Why did you lie?
Neden yalan söyledin?
She killed herself, right?
Kadın kendini öldürdü, değil mi?
Since she had gunshot residue on her hand,
Elinde barut kalıntısı olduğu için
your lawyer figured she had killed herself.
avukatın kadının kendini öldürdüğünü anladı
However, you insisted that you had shot her.
ama kadını senin öldürdüğün konusunda ısrar ettin.
She asked you to kill her, didn't she?
Senden onu öldürmeni istedi, değil mi?
Bullseye! I'm right, aren't I?
Tam isabet! Bildim, değil mi?
I knew it. It wasn't you who shot her, was it?
Biliyordum. Onu sen vurmadın, değil mi?
I bet this is what she said, "Shoot me."
Eminim "Vur beni" demiştir.
Shoot me.
Vur beni.
Don't look at me like that!
Bana öyle bakma!
Kill me! Please kill me!
Öldür beni! Lütfen öldür beni!
Martin!
Martin!
I didn't do it! She shot herself!
Ben yapmadım! Kendini vurdu!
I didn't do it!
Ben yapmadım!
Right? It wasn't me! Right?
Tamam mı? Ben yapmadım! Tamam mı?
That's right, isn't it? Amazing! I got it right.
Doğru, değil mi? Harika! Doğru bildim!
You're wrong.
Yanılıyorsun.
You deserted her.
Onu terk ettin.
You gave her what she wanted.
İstediğini verdin.
-You're wrong. -Then what about your mother?
-Yanılıyorsun. -Peki ya annen?
Your mother froze to death when you were ten years old, right?
Sen 10 yaşındayken annen donarak öldü, değil mi?
You deserted your mother too.
Anneni de terk ettin.
I'm right about that too! Amazing!
Bunu da bildim. Harika!
This is amazing. I can really see these things!
Süper oldu. Bunları gerçekten görüyorum.
Every day, you carried your alcoholic mother back home.
Alkolik anneni her gün eve taşıdın.
Isn't that right? Your mother would always tell you,
Öyle değil mi? Annen sana hep şöyle derdi,
"Leave me here."
"Beni burada bırak"
Even so, you carried her home every day.
Yine de onu her gün eve taşıdın
But one night…
ama bir gece…
No, you can't sleep here!
Hayır, burada uyuyamazsın!
I'll be fine. Just fine.
Bir şey olmaz, olmaz.
Just leave me here.
Beni burada bırak.
Wake up!
Uyan!
You left her there.
Onu orada bıraktın!
Isn't that right? You left your mother there.
Değil mi? Anneni orada bıraktın.
The next day, you were notified that your mother froze to death.
Sonraki gün annenin donarak öldüğü haberini aldın
But this is what you thought then, "It wasn't my fault."
ama o an şöyle düşündün, "Benim suçum değil.
"I only did that because she asked me to leave her there."
Onu bırakmamı istediği için onu bıraktım sadece"
You're exactly right. It wasn't your fault.
Sonuna kadar haklısın. Senin suçun değildi.
Both your mother and your drug-addict girlfriend wanted to die.
Annen de uyuşturucu bağımlısı sevgilin de
These people wanted to die, so you simply let them.
O insanlar ölmek istedi ve sen de onları terk ettin.
You didn't do anything wrong. What you did was right.
Yanlış bir şey yapmadın. Sen doğru olanı yaptın.
You released them from the misery of life.
Onları hayatın ızdırabından kurtardın.
Eva too. She wants to die as well.
Eva'yı da. O da ölmek istiyor.
Just then, the devil came.
İşte o an iblis geldi.
I didn't look at the devil as we passed by one another.
İblis yanımdan geçerken onun yüzüne bakmadım.
Don't look.
Bakma.
Don't you dare look.
Sakın ha bakma.
I repeated that to myself like a child would.
Bir çocuk gibi kendi kendime bunu tekrarladım.
Subtitle translation by: Brian Athey
Alt yazı çevirmeni: Ömür Gencer